delighted.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy – Delighted

Updated May 9, 2018 

##  What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. 

##  What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

###  To personalize your experience: 

Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. We present the responses from your customers as well as personal data you provide us when you access our service. 

###  To improve our website: 

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

###  To improve customer service: 

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

###  To process transactions: 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

###  To create reports: 

From time to time we may use aggregate non-identifying information to create reports or info-graphics for public consumption. 

###  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

We may reach out from time to time with questions for you about your use of Delighted. We may also run contests which you may be eligible for which we will contact you about. 

###  To send periodic emails: 

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

##  How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information conﬁdential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, ﬁnancials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

##  Do we use cookies? 

Yes. Cookies are small ﬁles that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traﬃc and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service. 

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identiﬁable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information conﬁdential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identiﬁable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

##  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

##  Your consent 

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

##  Contacting us 

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Delighted, LLC  
1027 Alma Street, Suite B  
Palo Alto, CA 94301  
USA 

##  Privacy Shield 

Delighted is a Covered Entity under the Qualtrics Privacy Shield certification 

Delighted will never transfer Data to a third-party without the written permission of the customer. In other words, there is no onward transfer. 

##  Complaints and Inquiries 

Delighted is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), and individuals have a right to contact the FTC regarding services provided by Delighted. 

If you are an EU or Swiss citizen, and have questions about your personal information that may have been collected in a Delighted survey, please contact the entity that created or sent you the survey. Delighted is not responsible for any Data collected and only processes Data as controlled by the customer. If the survey creator is unresponsive with your inquiry, please contact the Delighted Concierge team. 

General inquiries regarding this policy, or any complaints regarding surveys that are unresolved by the survey creator, may be sent to the Delighted concierge team at [hello@delighted.com](mailto:hello@delighted.com). There is no charge for this inquiry. 

Delighted has a team of legal and technical staff to maintain compliance with this policy. For legal inquiries, please contact: [legal@delighted.com](mailto:legal@delighted.com)

Independent Recourse Mechanism: Any disputes are handled by the International Centre for Dispute Resolution (details below). Inquiries are free of charge. 

##  Information Related to Privacy Shield 

For details about the Privacy Shield program: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

Delighted complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Delighted has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. 

The key goals of Privacy Shield are to inform individuals, both EU and Swiss individuals, about: 

the right of individuals to access their personal data the choices and means your organization offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal data the requirement for your organization to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements Delighted’s Privacy Shield self-certification does not cover human resources data. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Delighted commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Delighted at: [legal@delighted.com](mailto:legal@delighted.com)

Delighted has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to the American Arbitration Association (AAA), an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the AAA for more information or to file a complaint (contact details below). The services of the AAA are provided at no cost to you. 

During the normal provisioning of the Delighted services, no data are transferred between geographical regions. All data are stored in a specific data center chosen by the customer/controller. If there is a case when personal data are transferred from the EU to the United States, it is solely for the purpose of processing as per instructions from the controller. 

Delighted provides appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alternation, unauthorized disclosure or access, and understands whether onward transfer is allowed. 

Because adequate protection is provided by Privacy Shield participants, contracts with Privacy Shield participants for mere processing do not require prior authorization (or such authorization will be granted automatically by the EU Member States), as would be required for contracts with recipients not participating in the Privacy Shield or otherwise not providing adequate protection. 

Delighted self-certifies with Privacy Shield. A self-assessment is signed by a company officer or other authorized representative of the organization at least once a year and made available upon request by individuals or in the context of an investigation or a complaint about non-compliance. Delighted is required to respond promptly to EU or Swiss individual inquiries, and other requests for information from the Department of Commerce relating to its adherence to the Privacy Shield Principles. 

Under Privacy Shield, an individual has the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding Privacy Shield compliance not resolved by any of the other Privacy Shield mechanisms. Under Privacy Shield, Delighted must respond to individual complaints within 45 days. For additional information, visit: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>

Delighted’s Independent Dispute Resolution (IDR) Provider is: 

American Arbitration Association   
International Centre for Dispute Resolution New York City, New York, USA   

U.S. Department of Commerce:   
<https://www.commerce.gov/news/fact-sheets/2016/07/fact-sheet-overview-eu-us-privacy-shield-framework>

Federal Trade Commission:   
<https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/press-releases/2016/02/statement-ftc-chairwoman-edith-ramirez-eu-us-privacy-shield-0>
